webbyplanet.com 2010-11-19

# Discount Code, coupons online COUPON CODE. Webbyplanet

## Privacy

### Our Commitment to Privacy

Webbyplanet.com (http://www.webbyplanet.com) is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets out our privacy policy and explains what we do with the personal information that we collect from our users.

### What Information Do We Collect?

When you visit our site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you actively choose to disclose ("Active Information") and use information collected, in a way not visible to you, on an aggregate anonymous basis as you and others browse our site ("Passive Information").

### Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

We never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

### Active Information You Choose to Provide

In order to receive coupons via email (become a "user"), we require you to disclose the following information: 

* Your name 

* Your email address

### Passive Information Collected 

Our site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" to collect information about how our site is used. Passive Information gathered may include the date and time of visits, the site pages viewed, time spent at our site, the sites visited just before and just after our site. Passive Information is collected on an aggregate basis without any association to your personal information so that you remain anonymous. If you do not wish to transmit "cookie" information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser

### How Does WEBBYPLANETt.com Use Your Personal Information? 

Webbyplanet.com collects personal information to provide you, the user, with the best and most personalized Web experience possible. We use that information to send you email newsletters and deal alerts. All emails, newsletters etc. will include special instructions in them to unsubscribe.

### What do I do if a coupon does not work?

If a coupon on our website is not working, please contact us using the link at the bottom of each page. After we receive your email, we will check the offer to verify if there was an error with the coupon code or if it has in fact expired. If the coupon has expired, keep checking our site. We update our site daily and as soon as we find another deal for that merchant, we will post it on our site.

### Your Information In Relation to Others We Link To

You are be able to access other websites through Webbyplanet.com. When you do so you are doing so subject to their policies regarding privacy and data collection and you should read those sites' privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such sites. When you choose to shop at such sites, you should read their privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before making purchases.

### Sharing Information with Advertisers or Other Third Parties

We may disclose anonymous information about user habits, characteristics and user patterns, based on aggregate user statistics to advertisers on our site.

### Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law

We may be required by law or government agency to disclose both Active and Passive Information you have provided to us.

### Who has access to your information?

No one has access to your information given to Webbyplanet except you and webbyplanet.com. No outside contractors or agent of Webbyplanet will ever have access to your information. All your information is password protected and cannot be accessed by anyone but you or webbyplanet.com.

### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an [email](http://www.webbyplanet.com/contact-us/).
